DECEMBER 20
Did you hear?
MIDDLE
JUMP
Apparently at Mid Jump, sexual content is okay
if it doesn't go on for more than four pages.
What? That sounds obscene.
Right. It is obscene.
The cover for that magazine
is obscene, as well.
Agreed. It is obscene, isn't it?
CHRISTMAS CAKE
ACCEPTING ORDERS
While we've been focused
on the culture festival,
the rest of the world
has gone into Christmas-mode.
NO OCCUPANCY
All these couples using Christmas Eve
as a pretext for hooking up...
No vacancies
at any of the love hotels.
NO OCCUPANCY
At the end of the day,
our world revolves around sex!
Awful! Awful! So obscene!
They all have nothing
but indecent thoughts on their minds!
And then... And then...
Indecent thoughts, huh?
What was that kiss, then?
There were...
all these tiny balloons everywhere!
SQUEAL SQUEAL
It was gorgeous beyond belief!
And then, President told me
to apply to Stanford!
That is, he ordered me
to join him in the U.S.!
Stanford?
I know! What was he thinking?
But the way he said it with that blush
on his face was just so adorable!
I said yes in spite of myself!
And in spite of myself, I kissed him!
Did you know, Hayasaka?
When you kiss someone you like,
it can't be a regular kiss!
LADY KAGUYA'S
KEY TIPS FOR KISSING
Class is now in session!
You place your lips together like so.
The grown-up way is to slip your tongue in.
Miss Kashiwagi and her boyfriend actually...
WAR CRIMINAL
So, you didn't know that,
did you, Hayasaka?
How cute.
Idi...
Idiot!
What?
DECEMBER 21
With the culture festival over,
the student council goes back to normal life.
Good work.
But the scars still
run deep.
Ishigami's here!
And Shirogane's battle
is far from over!
I let her know how I feel!
I even kissed her!
And it was a pretty intense one!
Meaning...
we can be considered
boyfriend and girlfriend now?
But how pure was that kiss, really?
If I'd mismanaged
the distance between us here...
What's this, President? One kiss,
and you're acting like my boyfriend?
That kiss only happened
because we were having a moment.
Surely you don't think
that a kiss makes us lovers now?
That's exactly how a cherry boy's mind would work.
CHERRY BOY
How cute.
GAH
President, are you all right?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
Today, I'm going to set things straight
with Shinomiya!
No matter what!
Here she comes!
DAINTY
TROT TROT
Hey, Shinomiya...
Wait, what?
Doesn't she seem different today?
Now that you mention it,
Oh... Oh... Oh... Oh... Oh...
she does look
more childish than usual.
Oh! Little Kaguya!
- Little Kaguya?
Little Kaguya! Little Kaguya! Little Kaguya!
I didn't think we'd get to see you this year!
Everyone! How lucky are we
to get to see Little Kaguya?
Wh-What the heck
do you mean by "Little Kaguya"?
Kaguya's personality undergoes slight shifts
depending on her mental state that day.
You're all aware of that, right?
Little Kaguya can only show up if she meets
the most stringent conditions.
60% happy, 40% in denial and, on top
of that, she has to be sleep-deprived.
IN DENIAL
Every single one of these boxes
needs to be checked.
LITTLE KAGUYA
And only when her psychological balance hits
that sweet spot does this rare Little Kaguya appear!
Rare Kaguya?
Even I've still only seen her three times!
How is this even possible?
That's right!
DECEMBER 20
The conditions had already been met
the previous night!
A grown-up kiss!
In a nutshell,
a dizzying array of kisses exist.
A kiss on the cheek or hand
signifying affection.
A kiss on the lips
indicating a close relationship.
And...
the more meaningful kind of kiss.
LOVE BIBLE
Isn't this the way
one normally kisses the one she loves?
KISSES THAT WORK
FOR ROMANCE
It says so in the books I've read.
Even Miss Kashiwagi and her boyfriend...
Miss Kashiwagi?
Yes?
Miss Kashiwagi...
Is that how one typically
goes about kissing another?
Huh? Um... Um—
That was a special kind of kiss
you only give to the person you love!
So whatever you do,
don't kiss anyone else like that, okay?
Understood!
War criminal.
Such disinformation was pumped
into Kaguya, a stranger to girl talk...
The kind of kiss you only give
to the one you love...
To the one you love!
And she ends up doing just that.
That was your first-ever kiss?
You aren't in a love scene
in a Hollywood movie!
In other words, it's a regular kiss, right?
Not by a long shot!
You shouldn't be kissing like that
on school grounds!
That's something
you should be doing in bed!
That kind of kiss...
practically amounts to having sex!
Se...
...x?
She managed to say it.
Wait!
What do you mean by "sex"?
All I did was insert my tongue
into his oral cavity!
That can't possibly be sex!
It's totally sex.
It's something you do
in the process of having sex.
Stop repeating the word "sex"!
You've been repeating it
yourself, Lady Kaguya!
Well, Christmas is around the corner.
Since you've gotten this far already,
it will be a breeze to take it
to the next level and have sex.
Good for you.
Wait! Why on earth would you go there?
Don't people normally wait at least a month or two
after their first kiss to engage in that sort of thing?
HOLLER HOLLER
It's a different story if you've already
gone that far with your first kiss!
HOLLER HOLLER
I'm just not getting through to you.
This is why children like you
who've never been kissed...
You're thinking of something
unbelievably infuriating right now, aren't you?
I'm getting nowhere with this!
Let me ask someone with experience
about what to actually expect!
MISS KASHIWAGI
NOW DIALING
Hello? Kaguya? What a surprise!
Is something wrong?
I'd like to ask you something,
Miss Kashiwagi.
What is it? Ask me anything!
Well, you see...
About how long did you wait
to have sex after your first kiss?
I-I'll have you know, Tsubasa and I
have never done anything so indec—
Please don't ridicule me!
I couldn't be more serious than I am now!
What?
This is a serious conversation?
After that first kiss,
maybe two months.
Of course! You'd wait
at least that long, right?
Then, how long after a grown-up kiss?
About 40 seconds.
Seconds?
Are you finally starting
to see the light, Lady Kaguya?
Just acknowledge it!
That because your first kiss was a deep dive,
chances are that President sees you
as a super-nympho lust monster!
A super-nympho lust monster?
How...
How can I possibly look him
in the eye tomorrow?
In an abrupt about-face
after that Ultra Romantic night,
THAT CAN'T POSSIBLY BE SEX!!
A SUPER-NYMPHO
LUST MONSTER!?
the point that Hayasaka brought up
has caused her to spend a night of agony!
MNGH
NNGH
And sleep-deprivation ensues!
Kaguya's brain plunges even further
into the depths of malfunction!
Resulting in two straight days of zero IQ!
Intellectually, it's Black Monday!
And...
Rare Kaguya?
Descent.
This is a hundred times better
than her being scary, so I accept it!
Whaaaaat?
Damn! Today of all days,
I really wanted to talk to Shinomiya!
In this state,
I can't even get through to her!
GRIND
This is bad!
Wh-Wh-What is it, Shinomiya?
Pwesident, good morning!
Actually, maybe it's perfect.
Who is this adorable creature?
Needless to say,
she's in a super-deformed state.
This is how she appears to everyone.
Tell me, how old are you, Little Kaguya?
Um... Um... Seventeen?
Seventeen, huh? What a sweetheart!
CONGRATULATIONS
ON COMING OF AGE
Did you know? If you're 17,
then next year, you'll be an adult!
It's not a good look to take advantage of someone
when they're vulnerable, Ishigami. So cut it out.
Oh!
So cuddly and fluffy!
I want to display you at my house!
SQUISH
WHACK
Ouch!
SQUISH
Hey! You can't hit people, you bad girl!
We just caught a glimpse
of Shinomiya's inner psyche, right?
Can't you see she doesn't like that?
SQUIRM
Just let her go, okay?
Oh, she's totally fine!
Little Kaguya loves me the best, don't you?
Go on, show us
who your favorites are in order!
Number one.
Huh?
Number two.
Number three.
What are you talking about?
Don't ask me, but I think
she just went with the flow there.
MINI DONUTS
Here.
What?
You're giving me a snack?
SMITTEN
Thanks!
Here.
Hey, thanks!
You're giving me one, too?
Oh...
RATTLE...
Sniff!
I'll run out and get some candy!
We're going at top speed,
so hang on, okay?
Listen, Shinomiya, about yesterday...
Pwesident...
You're breathing!
We're the same!
It's no good. We can't talk like this.
Right now, it seems like Shinomiya's brain
is the size of an orange.
She's probably seeing a different world than I am.
Come to think of it, I've heard
that if the gap between your IQ is 20 or so,
there's no way
you can hold a conversation.
In that case...
Chinomiya!
Pwesident?
Chinomiya, let's talk!
Okay! Let's!
What should we talk about?
Anything you want!
Chinomiya! Chinomiya!
Pwesident! Pwesident!
Chinomiya!
Pwesident! Pwesident! Pwesident!
They're holding a conversation,
and it's scarily devoid of substance.
I'm sorry I'm late—
Chinomiya! Chinomiya!
Pwesident! Pwesident!
Chinomiya! Chinomiya! Chinomiya! Chinomiya!
Pwesident! Pwesident! Pwesident! Pwesident!
Aren't you both too old
to be doing whatever this is?
Super-deformed is just super-deformed.
DECEMBER 20
Three days until Christmas Eve!
Having shared a grown-up kiss,
these two are about to see the curtain go up
on this year's final romantic battle of minds!
For Hayasaka, it was the morning from hell.
Little Kaguya's fast asleep, huh?
I'm not surprised.
MNGH
NNGH
The culture festival must've worn her out.
Let's let her get some real rest.
BAKED
SENBEI
MIDDLE
JUMP
Hey, almost forgot.
I brought this week's Mid Jump.
Great! Thank you!
TWO PUNCH MAN
MS. KUBO
DOESN'T MAKE IT
COMPLICATED
That's lewd material you have there.
I'm confiscating it.
Where'd you come from, Iino?
Look, Iino...
can you at least wait
until President finishes it?
Negative! The rules are the rules!
You only have yourself to blame
for bringing in contraband!
It's the same old, same old, huh?
Makes you wonder if it's going to be
like this until we graduate.
We're going to be
at each other's throats until the end.
I have no idea why...
but whenever you do something to me,
I can't rest until I get back at you.
What?
If you promise never to bring
anything like this again,
I'll let you have your book back.
Just keep your word on that,
and the odds of us getting along might be...
more than...
zero.
That's not going to happen.
I'm so going to bring another one next week.
How do you not see
that it's your own fault?
PUNCH
MISS
Seriously? What's going on here?
Are you stupid? Are you?
An old-school brawl?
Ouch! I'll bring it, no matter what!
Ts-Tsubame!
Don't mind us, please.
We're always like this.
After I made such a huge concession...
Well, if you say so.
Oh, right! There's something
I wanted to ask you, Yu.
What is it?
Do you think you'll be free
on Christmas Eve?
What is this? No way!
U-Um, if you don't feel like it,
you can totally say no, okay?
Wanna come over that day?
I'll be there!
Yay!
YAY
Whoa, Tsubame's house? On Christmas?
In Tsubame's room?
That's beyond perverted!
Oh! It's not like that!
I was planning to invite you, too, Iino!
For a threesome?
No! I'll be inviting a lot of people!
I'm going to throw a party!
It's an orgy!
Shut up, you clueless
Disciplinary Committee member!
How do you not get that she's talking
about a Christmas party?
O-O-Oh!
Oh, sorry. That just never crossed
my mind when I said it.
Hey, if Iino wasn't around,
I totally would've gotten the wrong idea, too.
I'm inviting the Cheerleading Squad
and the Culture Festival Committee.
Rei says she'll be coming, too!
Rei?
Tsubame!
All right, I'm in the middle
of an errand here...
so let me know if you're coming!
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
Hey, Ishigami...
Are you free on Christmas Eve?
Wanna come over that day?
Oh, are you having a Christmas party?
I'm surprised you made the connection.
So, let's have a Christmas party for everyone in the
student council! I'll provide my home as the venue!
You'll come, too, won't you, Kaguya?
MNGH
NNGH
That's a yes!
Isn't she just moaning in her sleep?
You won't have to spend another lonely Eve
all by yourself this year, Ishigami!
Thanks to Chika,
your brilliant event planner—
Hey, sorry, Senpai...
but on Christmas Eve,
I've got plans.
It's kind of a shame that your howls of laughter
will go to waste, but it's the truth.
It really is true.
Tsubame just invited Ishigami and me.
What?
You can't possibly turn down an invitation
from Tsubame, can you, Ishigami?
A BIT DISAPPOINTED
Huh? Why couldn't I, if it's her?
Everyone here is aware
that you have a crush on Tsubame.
Yeah.
Well, yes.
No way!
Since when?
Maybe around the sports festival?
No way!
So...
which party are you going to, Iino?
Well, I know you think
I'd be a thorn in your side. So I guess I'll...
Huh? I don't think that.
Is... that right?
Huh?
GOOD NIGHT!!
SEE YOU LATER
IINO AND I WILL BOTH
ATTEND YOUR
CHRISTMAS PARTY
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT
I have to give him my answer
three months from now, huh?
LOST AND FOUND
IF NO ONE'S CLAIMED IT
IN THREE MONTHS, TAKE IT!
If no one's claimed it
in three months, huh?
Not that I really want it.
Christmas, huh?
I wonder what Shinomiya's going to do.
The second battle of minds
inside her own brain and the trial begin!
TWO GENIUSES' WAR OF LOVE
WHAT? I'M UP!?
Not only did the defendant steal a kiss
from Miyuki Shirogane without warning,
THE ACCUSED KAGUYA (STUPID)
but she even inserted her tongue,
of all things.
She is therefore charged with the crime proscribed
in article 174 of our personal penal code...
The Grown-Up Kiss Offensive.
In addition, the defendant is deemed
a flight risk who may flee the country.
Therefore, the prosecution seeks
the death penalty for the defendant.
THE COMPLETE
SIX CODES
OF JAPAN
PROSECUTOR KAGUYA
(COLD AS ICE)
Death penalty?
COUNSEL KAGUYA SHINOMIYA
No objections.
My own lawyer won't even defend me?
Pwesident is in the student council room...
Wow, it's perfect!
Uttering gibberish
in front of President...
Number one...
NUMBER ONE
S-Saying he was your number one!
I don't remember.
Well, what a convenient mind you have!
Well, why is it such a big deal?
President used all those balloons
to let me know how he feels!
What's wrong with that?
W-Well, you do have a point, but—
How ludicrous.
Why are you letting
mere balloons rattle you?
AHHH
You're not looking like yourself, either!
My internal breakers broke, too.
All right.
Playtime is over.
You've been summoned today so that
we can decide what to do going forward.
This is a crucial decision
that will determine our future.
PRESIDING JUDGE KAGUYA
(CHILD)
There are three issues under discussion.
(1) ON OUR RELATIONSHIP WITH PRESIDENT
(2) ON STUDYING ABROAD
(3) ON THAT GROWN-UP KISS
Let us resolve them one by one.
First of all...
our relationship with President.
Come on, we've got to be lovers now!
I mean, we've kissed!
R-Right, we are, aren't we?
SMOOCH
Don't be ridiculous.
If kissing makes you lovers,
then sex workers would be lovers with everyone.
I have to agree.
Although our feelings are undeniably mutual,
we've never been vocal about them.
If we're to take it to the next level,
we should say so directly.
Then regarding Number 1,
our conclusion must be...
(1) ON OUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH MIYUKI SHIROGANE
A.
MORE THAN
FRIENDS
LESS THAN
LOVERS
Next, let's discuss studying abroad!
(2) ON STUDYING ABROAD
Well, President did say
it was a once-in-a-lifetime wish!
I'm so going!
Yes.
Are you serious?
Huuuh?
You don't seriously believe
you'll be allowed to do such a thing, do you?
How do you plan to talk Father into it?
Well...
Consider it a blessing that you've been able
to distance yourself from him.
You must refrain at all costs from doing anything
that would awaken the sleeping tiger.
But I already told him I'd go.
Keeping your promises, no matter what.
You need something in your life
that you can have absolute faith in.
Isn't that the policy you live by?
Do whatever you want. However...
when you fail, it might be
the last time I ever see your face.
(2) ON STUDYING ABROAD
A.
GO WITH
PRESIDENT
And finally, regarding that grown-up kiss...
what are we going to do about it?
Seriously, what are we going to do? Well?
President might be thinking
that I'm a super-nympho lust monster!
I mean it, what are we going to do?
All you have to do is explain yourself.
That you just misread the situation.
But that would be embarrassing!
I think it would be better
to take the stance of a grown-up woman!
A KISS?
THAT'S NO MORE
THAN A GREETING
What a ludicrous conversation.
That's why you never should've kissed him.
In the first place, a kiss is something
that the man should seek.
A woman going for a kiss...
How disgraceful is that!
I think you're being sexist!
She's right! Who decided
that a woman can't kiss first?
You have no clue, do you?
I'd rather have a kiss stolen from me,
not the other way around!
Huh?
What? But why?
Because it would make my heart
pound harder that way!
We all have different fetishes!
Kissing impulsively...
We're not beasts in the wild!
IRRITATED
Would it kill you to learn a little restraint?
It's only natural to want
to kiss someone you're in love with!
That's right! If you really love someone,
there's just no holding back!
You can say stuff like that
because you're not in love with President, Ice!
Me...
not in love with...
Miyuki Shirogane?
You happy-go-lucky insurgents...
You can't see the forest for the trees
because you put your own feelings first!
You have no idea how much I've held back!
How I've continued to hold back all this time!
It was none other than I
who first fell in love with Miyuki Shirogane!
More than you two ever have!
I'm also the one who's the most serious
about my future with him!
Here I am, racking my brain
to find a way to make him mine,
yet you both keep doing as you please!
How arrogant of you,
you Kaguya-come-latelys!
Hey, hold up.
Don't argue with yourself. It's just sad.
Right! In the first place, it doesn't matter
who fell in love with him first!
I mean, aren't you even happy
that President kissed you?
Oh, would you shut up?
It's like your brains
are in la-la land, you morons!
Don't you dare lecture me!
I've been longing all this time
for President to kiss me!
So, what were you thinking?
Go die and rot in hell!
For once in your lives,
consider my feelings, too!
Oh, this isn't good.
Are you sure
you want to conceal the real you?
Are you awake, Shinomiya?
Morning.
Yes.
It seems I've been fast asleep for a while.
Huh?
Good morning, Shirogane.
I'd appreciate a cup of coffee, please.
I'm throwing
a Christmas party at
my place this year.
Wanna come?
Hmm, I'll come
if I can make it.
Sis texted me
that Kaguya will be there.
I'M COMING